Daas Hatweek

Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates | (+971) 54 215 6858 | hatweekdaas@gmail.com | Linkedin | Portfolio

SUMMARY

Favorably motivated Software Engineer with over **3** years of experience in software development, specializing in Django and Django Rest Framework for server-side logic and React JS for client-side. Proficient in foundational programming principles with a drive to craft high-performing web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

NanoVoltz, Full Stack Web Developer

April 2024 - Present

Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates

- Work closely with a dynamic team of developers to create a sophisticated real-time vehicle tracking system, ensuring seamless integration and high performance.
- Led the design of the application UI and Admin dashboard using Figma, focusing on user-friendly interfaces and intuitive navigation.
- Implement the designs using React JS and Material-UI (MUI) to deliver a responsive and visually appealing user experience
- Architect and develop a robust server infrastructure for efficient data reception, processing, and real-time analysis using Python Django and Django Rest Framework.

AL-Wadi Medical Center, Full Stack Developer

Dec. 2022 - Sept. 2023

Homs, Syria

- Led a team of 3 developers in developing a comprehensive platform digitizing medical operations.
- Developed a web and mobile applications using MySQL, Django Rest Framework, Flutter, React, and Figma.
- Ensured 100% secure data handling and seamless integration between applications.
- Conducted thorough unit tests, resulting in a 95% test coverage across both applications.

Freelanceer, Full Stack Developer

Feb. 2021 - March 2024

Remote

- Spearheaded development for 6 projects, prioritizing robust backend solutions using Django and Django REST framework.
- Designed user interfaces for 3 web applications, leading to a 20% improvement in user engagement metrics.
- Managed 2 projects simultaneously, meeting 100% of deadlines and deliverables effectively.
- Implemented automated testing protocols, resulting in a 30% reduction in bug occurrences across all projects.

EDUCATION

Al-Baath University - Bachelor of Science

Homs, Syria Nov. 2023

Informatics Engineering Department of Software Engineering and Information Systems

Graduated in the top 10 of the class and achieved the highest score on the National Exam in the college

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Python, JavaScript, C++

Back End Development: Diango, Diango Rest Framework, Flask, Fast API, Node JS

Front End Development: React JS, Redux, HTML5, CSS3, Vue JS, MUI, Bootstrap, WordPress

Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, Mongo DB

DevOps and Tools: Version Control Systems (Git), Azure, Docker, Kubernetes, JIRA, Scrum, CI/CD pipelines

Architecture and Technologies: MVC, RESTFull APIs, Microservices, WebSocket, RabbitMQ **Additional Tools & Skills**: Agile Methodologies, Figma (UI/UX design), SEO optimization tools.

Machine Learning: Scikit-learn, PyTorch

Languages

- English Fluent
- Arabic Native